Oh, yeah it is.
Hadn't really paid attention to it.
You were the one that called about the jar, right?
Yeah, that was me.
Cool, well, here you go.
She handed me a very small, glass mason jar.
It couldn't have been more than two inches tall.
Inside of it was a light.
Not a light bulb, just light.
It was like someone bottled up sunshine.
It glowed even in the mid-afternoon daylight.
It looked like a tiny sun, or a tiny universe existing in this little crystal-walled home.
I was admiring it with no attempt to hide the awe on my face.
Pretty rad, isn't it?
What, what is it?
I asked that, like, three different times, I think.
My answer is still the same.
It is happiness.
Happiness in a glass jar.
What do I do with it?
Keep it, she said simply, if you have any problems shoot me a text.
She started to get into her car.
Wait, I said, I thought you were selling this?
How much is it?
Don't worry, man, she said with a smile, you'll pay.
She closed her door and I stepped out of her way as she backed up, then drove off.
What the hell had just happened?
What was I holding?
I looked down at the jar again, its radiance was simply mesmerizing.
I put it in my pocket and could see its glow slightly through my pants.
I began to walk home.
What was just a nice, sunny day, quickly changed into a rainy one with clouds wrapping the
sky.
It was not forecasted that it would rain, or else I would've ridden the bus or subway
to work that day.
I jogged home trying not to get too drenched.
I finally found shelter once I made it to my apartment building.
I walked up to my door and found that my key wasn't on my key ring anymore.
Shit, I can't believe I lost it again, I thought.
I knocked on the door and said in a somewhat loud voice, hey babe it's me, I don't know
what happened to my key.
I heard the door being unlocked from the other side.
When the door opened, I was greeted by a large, heavy set man with greasy hair and unkempt
goatee.
He said, I think you got the wrong door, bud.
Oh, I said, disoriented, my bad, sorry, have a good one.
He let out a chuckle as he closed the door.
Apartment number 33, I know that was my apartment.
I know it was.
I'd been in apartment 33 for 5 years now.
But that was not my apartment.
From what I could see inside, all the furniture was different, it was painted a different
color, it was all wrong.
I felt like I'd hit my head and was drugged.
In that moment, nothing made sense.
I pulled out my phone to call Kelsey so she could calm me down and tell me I just got
confused for a second.
But her contact wasn't in my phone.
In fact, nothing was in my phone.
I had no messages with her.
No previous calls, no pictures, it was like my phone reset to its factory settings.
Did that girl somehow switch my phone out when I wasn't looking?
I would've just dialed Kelsey's number manually, but I couldn't quite remember it.
I had known it by heart before, but not anymore.
I needed to get back to the office, I had all my contacts backed up on my work computer.
Since it was still raining, I hopped on the bus which had a stop right in front of the
apartment complex.
I rode downtown toward my office, the whole time staring at my wet shoes, wondering what
the hell was going on.
We have a keycard access to our building so only authorized personnel can get inside.
I always keep my access card in my wallet, always.
But surprise, surprise, it wasn't there.
I buzzed into the speaker we had for guests with appointments or employees as a backup
in case anyone lost or forgot their card.
BZZZ.
Hey this is Tim, I must've lost my card.
My employee number is...
I stopped as I drew a blank.
A voice came through the speaker, Tim, you got cut out, what's your employee number?
Um, I can't remember, I...